So Malia Obama is dropping Obama as her
last name and people are saying it's
because she wants to live her own life.
She wasn't she doesn't want to be
attached to, you know, being a nepo
baby,
etc. I don't think that's
it. This generation has a very keen
sense of morality. um they are very
clear on information in ways that
generations previous to them were not.
And her generation, I'm sure, has made
it abundantly clear to her that her
father was a wararmonger, that her
father did not deserve any Nobel Peace
Prize because he was actually bombing
the sh out of Yemen and that her father
was the porter chief. I promise you that
she is at an age where she's
realizing this last name attaches me to
imperialism and empire. And I'm sorry,
but I can tell by that hair and that
scarf around her neck, she ain't about
that life. Mm- And she a
writer. Baby girl is like, "Y'all, I
ain't really rocking with y'all. You can
have them secrets over there. I want my
own life and I do not want to be
attached to your legacy of American
harm. Just my theory. What do you all
think?
[Music]